<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quickstart Guide for Tratteria on Tratteria</title>
    <link>https://tratteria.io/docs/quickstart/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Quickstart Guide for Tratteria on Tratteria</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://tratteria.io/docs/quickstart/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Running Tratteria</title>
      <link>https://tratteria.io/docs/quickstart/running-tratteria/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tratteria.io/docs/quickstart/running-tratteria/</guid>
      <description>This quick-start guide outlines the steps to set up and run Tratteria for initial learning and evaluation purposes.
Getting the Repository
Quick-Start Configuration
Running as a Native Go Server
Running as a Docker Container
Getting the Repository To get started, clone the Tratteria repository from GitHub:
git clone https://github.com/SGNL-ai/Tratteria Quick Start Configuration Tratteria is configured using a YAML file. The quick-start configuration can be found at:
https://github.com/SGNL-ai/tratteria/blob/main/example-configs/config.quick-start.yaml
The file contains the below configuration:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generatting TraTs</title>
      <link>https://tratteria.io/docs/quickstart/generating-trats/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tratteria.io/docs/quickstart/generating-trats/</guid>
      <description>This guide explains how to generate TraTs (TraTs) using Tratteria after its successful setup, as described in the Running Tratteria guide.
Overview
TraTs Request Parameters
TraTs Request
TraTs Response
Overview Once Tratteria is running, either as a native Go server or inside a Docker container, you can generate TraTs (TraTs). The service is accessible at localhost:9090 and provides the http endpoint POST /token_endpoint for token generation.
TraTs Request Parameters To request TraTs (TraTs), the following parameters must be provided in the request:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Verifying TraTs</title>
      <link>https://tratteria.io/docs/quickstart/verifying-trats/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tratteria.io/docs/quickstart/verifying-trats/</guid>
      <description>This guide details the steps to verify Transaction Tokens (TraTs) after successfully generating them as per the Generating TraTs guide.
Overview
Accessing Tratteria&amp;rsquo;s Public Key JSON Web Key Sets (JWKS)
Verifing TraTs
Overview TraTs are cryptographically signed by Tratteria&amp;rsquo;s private key and are verifiable using Tratteria&amp;rsquo;s public key.
Accessing Tratteria&amp;rsquo;s Public Key JSON Web Key Sets (JWKS) Tratteria&amp;rsquo;s signing key can be generated seperately and supplied through the configuration, or if not provided, it is automatically generated by Tratteria.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
