<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Installing Tratteria on Tratteria</title>
    <link>https://tratteria.io/docs/installation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Installing Tratteria on Tratteria</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://tratteria.io/docs/installation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Installing Tconfigd</title>
      <link>https://tratteria.io/docs/installation/installing-tconfigd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tratteria.io/docs/installation/installing-tconfigd/</guid>
      <description>Tconfigd is a central daemon that manages Tratteria configurations. To get started with Tratteria, we first need to install Tconfigd. Please follow the instructions from Tconfigd&amp;rsquo;s installation readme to install Tconfigd.
After successfully installing Tconfigd, you should be able to see a running Tconfigd pod in the tratteria-system namespace.
kubectl get pod -n tratteria-system Output:
NAME READY STATUS RESTARTS AGE tconfigd-85c5697c9b-4lx4s 1/1 Running 0 88s Next, proceed to deploy Tratteria service, an open-source service for managing Transaction Tokens (TraTs).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying Tratteria Service</title>
      <link>https://tratteria.io/docs/installation/deploying-tratteria/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tratteria.io/docs/installation/deploying-tratteria/</guid>
      <description>Tratteria Service is an open source Transaction Tokens (TraTs) Service. It is responsible for generating TraTs.
Tconfigd runs in its own dedicated namespace and is cluster-specific. But, the Tratteria service operates in the application namespace. We must deploy different Tratteria services for different application environments or namespaces.
Please follow the instructions from Tratteria&amp;rsquo;s deployment readme to deploy Tratteria service.
After successfully deploying Tratteria service, you should be able to see running Tratteria service pods in the application namespace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up Tratteria Agents</title>
      <link>https://tratteria.io/docs/installation/setting-up-tratteria-agents/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tratteria.io/docs/installation/setting-up-tratteria-agents/</guid>
      <description>Tratteria Agents are sidecar container agents that verify TraTs in microservices.
Tratteria agents are injected into microservices pods to verify TraTs. To integrate Tratteria agents into microservices, follow the instructions from Tratteria Agent&amp;rsquo;s readme.
After successfully integrating Tratteria Agents, you should be able to see running Tratteria agent sidecars alongside your application microservices pods. For example, below are the running Order service pods from the Tratteria example application&amp;rsquo;s dev environment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
